<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-02-15T01:08:43+00:00</updated><id>/blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Random Bits of Rob</title><subtitle>Whatever random bit comes to mind</subtitle><author><name>Rob Tuck</name></author><entry><title type="html">First Post</title><link href="/blog/general%20thoughts/first-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="First Post" /><published>2023-02-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-02-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/blog/general%20thoughts/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="/blog/general%20thoughts/first-post/"><![CDATA[<p>This is another attempt at blogging for me.  I tried this once before when I was ill in 2015-2016, but gave up once I was healthy.  Not sure what the motivation is this time … boredom, the need to create something, a writing exercise, heading towards 50 … I suppose those are all valid reasons.</p>

<p>It will be a personal experiment in collecting various thoughts.  It might be something as stupid as me talking about my shitty guitar playing or some course I’m taking.  Maybe I’ll go off on some rant about politics or just delve into some odd topic that has currently grabbed my attention.  If someone finds it interesting, wonderful.  If some think it’s stupid and boring, then just change the channel.</p>]]></content><author><name>Rob Tuck</name></author><category term="General Thoughts" /><category term="General Thoughts" /><category term="nothing in particular" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is another attempt at blogging for me. I tried this once before when I was ill in 2015-2016, but gave up once I was healthy. Not sure what the motivation is this time … boredom, the need to create something, a writing exercise, heading towards 50 … I suppose those are all valid reasons. It will be a personal experiment in collecting various thoughts. It might be something as stupid as me talking about my shitty guitar playing or some course I’m taking. Maybe I’ll go off on some rant about politics or just delve into some odd topic that has currently grabbed my attention. If someone finds it interesting, wonderful. If some think it’s stupid and boring, then just change the channel.]]></summary></entry></feed>